[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the natural habitat of the snows leopard, that was hunted down for its beautiful fur, as a result of which its population went down to 1,000 animals in the 1960s?", "correct_answer": "Central Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["North America", "Central Asia and North America", "Europe and North America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many recognized constellations are there in Earth\u2019s entire view?", "correct_answer": "88", "incorrect_answers": ["244", "106", "33"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1983, riding on board the Challenger, she became the first American woman in space.", "correct_answer": "Sally Ride", "incorrect_answers": ["Judith Resnik", "Jerrie Cobb", "Sharon Christa McAuliffe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Fletch, Alan Stanwyk persuades Fletch to kill him by telling him that he is dying of cancer and wants to avoid a slow painful death. Fletch agrees to kill Alan for how much?", "correct_answer": "$50,000", "incorrect_answers": ["$5,000", "$10,000", "$100,000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays Mr. Wong in the comedy film Norbit?", "correct_answer": "Eddie Murphy", "incorrect_answers": ["Dave Chappelle", "Cuba Gooding Jr.", "Chris Tucker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 2003 movie plot consisted of a fast spreading virus that locked its victims into a permanent state of murderous rage?", "correct_answer": "28 Days Later", "incorrect_answers": ["Resident Evil", "The Last Horror Movie", "Dawn of the Dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these people is the Austrian biologist and physician who first identified the four basic blood types?", "correct_answer": "Karl Landsteiner", "incorrect_answers": ["Felix Bernstein", "William Osler", "Charles Richard Drew"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "It is practically impossible to drown unwillingly in the Dead Sea.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what California area was the 1982 film Poltergeist primarily shot?", "correct_answer": "Aqoura Hills", "incorrect_answers": ["Hollywood", "Laguna Beach", "Ft Lauderdale"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Journey to the Center of the Earth, who leads the daring quest to the Earths core?", "correct_answer": "Oliver S.  Lindenbrook", "incorrect_answers": ["Ronan G. Quinn", "Colin A. Jenkins", "Malcolm  L. Mac Phail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Besides friendship, what is the relationship between Roul Duke and Dr. Gonzo in the movie Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas?", "correct_answer": "Dr. Gonzo is Dukes attorney", "incorrect_answers": ["Dr. Gonzo is Dukes psychiatrist", "Dr. Gonzo is Dukes brother", "Dr. Gonzo is Dukes physician"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turtles can breathe underwater.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]